<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"
xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
>
<channel>
<title><![CDATA[ScarppingTest]]></title>
<atom:link href="http://afru.shop/?feed=test%20scrap" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
<link>http://afru.shop</link>
<description><![CDATA[Just another WordPress site]]></description>
<language>en-US</language>
<sy:updatePeriod>daily</sy:updatePeriod>
<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9</generator>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Seniorcareto]]></title>
<link>https://www.seniorcareto.com</link>
<description><![CDATA[Seniors are a select group of people that need extra care. Therefore, they usually have a line of products specifically made for them. One of these is the microwave. In case you are looking for the perfect microwave for a senior member of your family, The Ponfish’s Post would be a good starting point. In&hellip; &lt;a class=&quot;more-link&quot; href=&quot;http://afru.shop/hello-world/&quot;&gt;Continue reading &lt;span class=&quot;screen-reader-text&quot;&gt;Hello world!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[  					<p>Seniors are a select group of people that need extra care. Therefore, they usually have a line of products specifically made for them. One of these is the microwave. In case you are looking for the perfect microwave for a senior member of your family, The Ponfish’s Post would be a good starting point. In this article, we will look at some of the questions people frequently ask about senior microwaves. I hope that these will help you settle on the best. Senior microwaves faqs What makes a microwave suitable for seniors? You have to understand that not all microwaves suit seniors. Here are some of the distinct features that…</p>				,  					<p>Best Cheap Gaming Laptops for Fallout 4 Under $500</p>				,  					<p>When we gave birth to our first child, Ellis, we bought Baby Jogger City Mini. He has been 19 months old and I cherish it very much. We live on the first floor in London, so I need a light carriage, which is difficult to carry everywhere. City Mini checked all containers. When I got the second smallest seat, 15 months later, it seemed easy to decide to get a dual format-one seat after another.</p>				,  					<p>If you have visited Facebook recently, you may have seen an ad for Mintlyfe Patch. The abdomen-sized peppermint extract uses the conductivity of sophorosides and transdermal technology to promote weight loss and fat removal. Each patch contains a cocktail of 56 ingredients, including mint, Korean ginseng and capsaicin. These ingredients are regarded as the key to quickly and safely get rid of fat accumulation and cellulite in the "fluffy" area. A big promise was made, so I decided to test…</p>				,  					<p>Can I continue breastfeeding after I return to work?Yes, you can. If you live in a nearby workplace or at a daycare center on site or nearby, you can take a break from nursing time to feed your baby. If this is not possible, there are two options:</p>				,  					<p>Are you wondering how to discover the fastest method of Yeezy Boost 700 Wave Runner (OG)?If you don’t mind adding another pair of stylish Yeezy to the spin, you should choose Yeezy Boost 700 OG.</p>				,  					<p>If you can&#039;t get a rating for the "Light Gray Yeezy Boost 750" launched on June 11, you may want to snap up a pair on eBay, Craigslist and other sites. Be sure to go out and buy things, but arm yourself as much as possible to avoid eventually getting counterfeit products.</p>				,  					<p>What&#039;s new in the artisan world? I am focused on helping you set up the craft exhibition. The appearance is beautiful but not crowded, and the attractive display determines whether the partons will stop or continue walking. I list some important elements and then discuss them in detail.</p>				,  					<p>If you are breastfeeding your baby and want to work again, you may need to start expressing milk and storing it for future use. Expression and storage can also make your routine more flexible. For the safety of infants, breast milk needs to be stored safely. Read tips on storing breast milk.</p>				,  					<p>The cost of family care is sufficient without losing more income during the trip. Working from home is an option that can help you provide parental care while still providing financial services. Although not everyone can choose, working from home is becoming more common. Working at home as a family carer: is it possible?</p>				,  					<p>I saw this article and thought it would be good information to pass on to you. We all thought we were done with vaccines once we reached adulthood. It’s important to check with your doctors to ensure you’re still up to date with important shots so you can proactively avoid some of the diseases that can be so detrimental to senior’s health. In the 1920s, the respiratory disease diphtheria was one of parents’ biggest fears for their children. In the United States, an estimated 100,000-200,000 cases of diphtheria per year caused 13,000-15,000 deaths, mainly children, in that decade (Wikipedia). Today, diphtheria vaccines have largely eradicated the disease from the United States.…</p>				,  					<p>What do you get Grandma this year? A new blanket . . . again? How about a pair of slippers? While those gifts could satisfy the needs or desires of a senior loved one, why not choose a present that is even more meaningful: a gift from the heart. While you may not be able to add the following 10 gift ideas to a shopping list, you can bet they’re on your loved one’s wish list. Take your loved one shopping. Whether a trip to the mall or an online shopping spree, make it a special day. Be sure to tune into your loved one’s limitations and don’t overdo. Lend…</p>				,  					<p>I am a member of the Society of Certified Senior Advisors and receive a monthly newsletter that always has articles I think you’ll find interesting. This one is for Seniors who are looking for jobs. The article offers some really good tips and resources for even more information. If you’re interested in being a CAREGiver or know somebody who is, Home Instead Senior Care is always looking for people. Visit our website at www.makeadifferenceforseniors.com for more information. ——————————————————————————————————————————————————- Not only has the 2008 recession put a dent in a lot of retirement accounts but people are living longer, so it makes financial sense to keep working as long as you can,…</p>				,  					<p>I regularly have the thrill of reading notes of gratitude from clients or their family members. It’s so satisfying to hear about how much our CAREGivers meant to them or how much they appreciated the responsiveness, availability, and sensitivity of the office team. However, the letter I received last week from a client’s daughter just took the cake…had me smiling for days. I don’t like to brag, BUT, I really want to share this letter as a tribute to my wonderful CAREGivers and office staff who were there for this family in so many ways. For those of you who make it all the way through the letter, thanks for…</p>				,  					<p>As I work with seniors, families and caregivers, we eventually have issues concerning clothing. Sometimes the issue is due to arthritic fingers that can no longer button, hook, tie or zip. Sometimes it is impaired vision, and they are unable to put outfits together or see the fabric colors.  Sometimes we have family members with dementia who take clothing off as soon as someone helps them get it on or who  just need the simple closure styles.  Frequently family members get frustrated because they do not know what to buy or where to shop.  I have used the Buck and Buck Catalog for years to help families deal with these…</p>				,  					<p>The Spectrum of Behaviors and Emotions Day by day we see residents that exhibit a complete spectrum of behaviors and/or emotions.  Situations that arise in the early morning, will certainly give way for something new by the afternoon.   This goes hand in hand with delivering quality dementia and Alzheimer’s care.  Providing an environment that allows for these rapid, daily changes is a challenging and daunting task. As well as, learning how to provide “happiness” and “comfort” to a person with a declining mental state. Happiness Defined Happiness can be defined as simply as this, “the satisfaction of needs.”  The needs, however, can change from age to age, year to year…</p>				,  					<p>Goat/Lifespan. How long do goats live as pets? Goats live an average of 7-14 years, depending on breed. Diet, living conditions, and other factors also affect the lifespan of the</p>				,  					<p>Washing with soap and water after outdoor activity may remove any chiggers that may be migrating on the skin and prevent their bites. Likewise, washing clothing that was worn outdoors</p>				,  					<p>Egg/Energy Amount. How much calories is in 2 eggs? How Many Calories in Two Eggs? An average serving size of two eggs contains only 148 calories or 620 kilojoules –</p>				,  					<p>What is this? Cold weather chickens can withstand temps around or slightly below freezing (32 degrees Fahrenheit to about ten degrees Fahrenheit). What temp is too cold for chickens? Chickens</p>				,  					<p>HOW TO GET RID OF APHIDS NATURALLY Remove aphids by hand by spraying water or knocking them into a bucket of soapy water. Control with natural or organic sprays like</p>				,  					<p>Duck/Lifespan. How long do ducks live as a pet? They are relatively long-lived pets—it&#039;s possible for them to live 10-15 years when well cared for. Keep in mind that they</p>				,  					<p>Harvest when seeds are plump and developed. Harvest when flower petals begin to dry out and fall off. Harvest when the back of flower turns from green to yellow (if</p>				,  					<p>What circumstances conspired to cause the Dust Bowl? Economic depression coupled with extended drought, unusually high temperatures, poor agricultural practices and the resulting wind erosion all contributed to making the</p>				,  					<p>What is a home remedy to get rid of yellow jackets? Mix 1 tablespoon of detergent and 2 cups of water. Alternatively, mix equal parts of water and liquid soap.</p>				,  					<p>The peanut, while grown in tropical and subtropical regions throughout the world, is native to the Western Hemisphere. It probably originated in South America and spread throughout the New World</p>				]]></content:encoded>
<guid isPermaLink="false">6271e443e6e78</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 02:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.seniorcareto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faqs.jpg" /></item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Senior Microwaves FAQ: You must know - Seniorcareto]]></title>
<link>https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faq/</link>
<description><![CDATA[Table of Contents Senior microwaves faqs What makes a microwave suitable for seniors? i) Easy controls ii) A large and bold display iii) Handle iv) Auto shut off v) Loud clicking sound Where can I buy good quality senior microwaves? What should I consider before getting a senior microwave? i) Simple design ii) Timer iii)&hellip; &lt;a class=&quot;more-link&quot; href=&quot;http://afru.shop/hello-world/&quot;&gt;Continue reading &lt;span class=&quot;screen-reader-text&quot;&gt;Hello world!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[  		<div id="ez-toc-container" class="ez-toc-v2_0_19 counter-hierarchy counter-decimal ez-toc-grey"> <div class="ez-toc-title-container"> <p class="ez-toc-title">Table of Contents</p> <span class="ez-toc-title-toggle"><a class="ez-toc-pull-right ez-toc-btn ez-toc-btn-xs ez-toc-btn-default ez-toc-toggle" style="display: none;"><i class="ez-toc-glyphicon ez-toc-icon-toggle"></i></a></span></div> <nav><ul class="ez-toc-list ez-toc-list-level-1"><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-1" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faq/#Senior_microwaves_faqs" title="Senior microwaves faqs">Senior microwaves faqs</a><ul class="ez-toc-list-level-3"><li class="ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-2" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faq/#What_makes_a_microwave_suitable_for_seniors" title="What makes a microwave suitable for seniors?">What makes a microwave suitable for seniors?</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-3" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faq/#i_Easy_controls" title="i) Easy controls">i) Easy controls</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-4" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faq/#ii_A_large_and_bold_display" title="ii) A large and bold display">ii) A large and bold display</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-5" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faq/#iii_Handle" title="iii) Handle">iii) Handle</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-6" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faq/#iv_Auto_shut_off" title="iv) Auto shut off">iv) Auto shut off</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-7" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faq/#v_Loud_clicking_sound" title="v) Loud clicking sound">v) Loud clicking sound</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-8" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faq/#Where_can_I_buy_good_quality_senior_microwaves" title="Where can I buy good quality senior microwaves?">Where can I buy good quality senior microwaves?</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-9" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faq/#What_should_I_consider_before_getting_a_senior_microwave" title="What should I consider before getting a senior microwave?">What should I consider before getting a senior microwave?</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-10" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faq/#i_Simple_design" title="i) Simple design">i) Simple design</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-11" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faq/#ii_Timer" title="ii) Timer">ii) Timer</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-12" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faq/#iii_Durability" title="iii) Durability">iii) Durability</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-13" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faq/#iv_Portability" title="iv) Portability">iv) Portability</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-14" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faq/#v_Power_consumption" title="v) Power consumption">v) Power consumption</a></li></ul></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-15" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faq/#Are_senior_microwaves_different_from_the_normal_ones" title="Are senior microwaves different from the normal ones?">Are senior microwaves different from the normal ones?</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-16" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faq/#Why_do_seniors_need_a_microwave" title="Why do seniors need a microwave?">Why do seniors need a microwave?</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-17" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faq/#Conclusion" title="Conclusion">Conclusion</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-18" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faq/#Key_Reference" title="Key Reference">Key Reference</a></li></ul></nav></div>  <p>Seniors are a select group of people that need extra care. Therefore, they usually have a line of products specifically made for them. One of these is the microwave. In case you are looking for the perfect microwave for a senior member of your family, The <a href="https://www.ponfish.com/top-best-countertop-microwaves-for-seniors/" data-wpel-link="exclude">Ponfish’s Post</a> would be a good starting point.</p><div class='code-block code-block-4' style='margin: 8px 0; clear: both;'> <div id="rc-widget-17a600" data-rc-widget data-widget-host="habitat" data-endpoint="//trends.revcontent.com" data-widget-id="269417"></div> <script type="text/javascript" src="https://assets.revcontent.com/master/delivery.js" defer="defer"></script> </div>     <p>In this article, we will look at some of the questions people frequently ask about senior microwaves. I hope that these will help you settle on the best.</p><div class='code-block code-block-1' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-19"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=19" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=19" defer></script></div></div>     <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Senior_microwaves_faqs"></span><strong>Senior microwaves faqs</strong><span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="What_makes_a_microwave_suitable_for_seniors"></span><strong>What makes a microwave suitable for seniors?</strong><span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="800" height="450" src="data:image/svg+xml,%3Csvg%20xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2000/svg'%20viewBox='0%200%20800%20450'%3E%3C/svg%3E" alt="What makes a microwave suitable for seniors?" class="wp-image-59" data-lazy- data-lazy- data-lazy-src="https://www.seniorcare2share.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/suitable-for-seniors.jpg" /><noscript><img loading="lazy" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.seniorcare2share.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/suitable-for-seniors.jpg" alt="What makes a microwave suitable for seniors?" class="wp-image-59"   /></noscript></figure></div>    <p>You have to understand that not all microwaves suit seniors. Here are some of the distinct features that you have to look out for:</p><div class='code-block code-block-2' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-28"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=28" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=28" defer></script></div></div>     <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="i_Easy_controls"></span>i) Easy controls<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <p>Having a full panel with many controls and buttons does not suit seniors. These microwaves have easy controls and switches for smoother operation. Most new models incorporate several features and advanced technology, which is quite pleasing but not conducive for seniors. You will find a knob control dial that turns quickly.</p><div class='code-block code-block-3' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-2"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=2" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=2" defer></script></div></div>     <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="ii_A_large_and_bold_display"></span>ii) A large and bold display<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <p>Most elders are visually challenged. Therefore, microwaves meant for seniors have a large and bold display to help them read the timer settings for smooth operation. Some of them also have bold printing on a white surface for more natural visibility.</p>    <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="iii_Handle"></span>iii) Handle<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <p>Seniors need to insert and remove food from the microwave, and therefore, the handle matters. Their microwaves have a pull handle, which is easy to open and does not need to much force. On the other hand, push handles are quite sophisticated and require too much force that seniors with underlying conditions cannot yield.</p>    <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="iv_Auto_shut_off"></span>iv) Auto shut off<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <p>It is easy for seniors to overcook and burn their foods since some of them are usually less alert. Therefore, their microwaves have an auto shut off feature which senses when the food is cooked and shuts off automatically.</p>    <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="v_Loud_clicking_sound"></span>v) Loud clicking sound<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <p>Seniors are usually less alert. Hearing problems also come with age. Therefore, their microwaves have a loud clicking sound to notify them when the food is already cooked. This is necessary, especially for the forgetful ones.</p>    <p>Recommended Post: <a href="https://www.seniorcare2share.com/holiday-gifts-seniors/" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer">10 Holiday Gifts Seniors Want But Won’t Ask For</a></p>    <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Where_can_I_buy_good_quality_senior_microwaves"></span><strong>Where can I buy good quality senior microwaves?</strong><span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="800" height="450" src="data:image/svg+xml,%3Csvg%20xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2000/svg'%20viewBox='0%200%20800%20450'%3E%3C/svg%3E" alt="Where can I buy good quality senior microwaves?" class="wp-image-62" data-lazy- data-lazy- data-lazy-src="https://www.seniorcare2share.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/Where-can-I-buy-good-quality-senior-microwaves.jpg" /><noscript><img loading="lazy" width="800" height="450" src="https://www.seniorcare2share.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/Where-can-I-buy-good-quality-senior-microwaves.jpg" alt="Where can I buy good quality senior microwaves?" class="wp-image-62"   /></noscript></figure>    <p>Senior microwaves are everywhere. Some of the most common sites include Amazon and Shopify. You can also choose to avoid the online approach and walk into reputable stores. This second approach allows you to assess and ascertain whether the microwave is meant for seniors.You can also make a direct order with the brand. If you are lucky enough, the brand will cover the shipping costs. However, make sure that you specify that you need a senior microwave.</p>    <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="What_should_I_consider_before_getting_a_senior_microwave"></span><strong>What should I consider before getting a senior microwave?</strong><span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <p>There are several brands offering these microwaves. You have to exercise care in your purchase. Here are some of the things that you need to look out for:</p>    <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="i_Simple_design"></span>i) Simple design<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <p>Ensure that the microwave you settle on comes devoid of complicated features that seniors may find challenging. Simple buttons and an excellent turning knob would be enough.</p>    <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="ii_Timer"></span>ii) Timer<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <p>The best microwave for seniors should have a timer to help monitor the heating of different foods. Remember, certain foods have heating requirements and duration of cooking that must be adhered to. A timer also makes cooking easy since most seniors cannot easily time themselves. Once the duration has elapsed, the microwave will either turn itself on or inform the user through a loud clicking sound.</p>    <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="iii_Durability"></span>iii) Durability<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <p>Durability is a factor that you should always look out for. The way your microwave is built will influence how long it lasts. If possible, settle on one made of stainless steel in both its interior and exterior. Stainless steel also keeps your microwave rust-free, which is one of the biggest destroyers of devices.</p>    <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="iv_Portability"></span>iv) Portability<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <p>Seniors cannot easily move the microwave around due to reduced strength. Make sure that you settle on a lighter model with a comfortable grip for more effortless adjustment or movement. The microwave should also be compact to occupy less space. Most seniors have <a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/142214" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer">dementia</a>, and having things lying around predisposes them to accidents that can be easily avoided.</p>    <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="v_Power_consumption"></span>v) Power consumption<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <p>Microwaves heat food, and as a result, some of them consume a lot of power. The best microwave for seniors should have an eco-mode for power conservation.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Are_senior_microwaves_different_from_the_normal_ones"></span><strong>Are senior microwaves different from the normal ones?</strong><span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p>Microwaves for seniors and the normal ones have the same functionality. They only differ in features. Senior microwaves tend to be more straightforward and basic as compared to their counterparts. You are likely going to get a fine turning knob and an easy to pull handle. They lack the sophistication seen in the regular microwaves. Most seniors suffer from several conditions that may affect their vision, hearing, or movement.</p>    <p>Related Post: <a href="https://www.seniorcare2share.com/four-vaccines-urged-for-seniors/" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer">Four Vaccines Urged for Seniors</a></p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Why_do_seniors_need_a_microwave"></span><strong>Why do seniors need a microwave?</strong><span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p>A microwave is a convenient means of food preparation, especially if the senior lives alone. Most of them have caregivers who are only available during the day. Microwaves are simpler to use compared to electric stoves. They do not require much time and effort since they come with a timer and an auto shut-off function. Most elders also have problems with their joints and cannot, therefore, sustain longer cooking hours.</p>    <p>Elders have reduced strength and cannot handle huge heating pans and pots, whereas food preparation in a microwave only requires basic settings. It is also a safe way of food preparation, which eliminates the risk of burns or accidents. Most utensils are microwave friendly, which is a good thing. Older adults won’t regularly wash loads of dishes., which can be cumbersome and annoying.</p>    <p>Lastly, most of these microwaves have menu options to help in cooking different types of food. All and elder needs to do is to place the plate of food into the microwave and wait.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Conclusion"></span><strong>Conclusion</strong><span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p>Microwaves meant for seniors have distinct features that make them conducive for meal preparation. I hope that this senior microwaves faqs article has answered some of the questions you had. In case you need more information about these machines.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Key_Reference"></span>Key Reference<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p>1.Tips for Seniors | FDA. <a href="https://www.fda.gov/media/83744/download" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer">Link</a></p>    <p>2.Food Safety for Older Adults – FDA. <a href="https://www.fda.gov/media/83744/download" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer">Link</a></p> <div class="related-posts"><h6>Related Posts</h6><ol><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/can-microwaves-explode/" title="Quick Answer: Can Microwaves Explode" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Can Microwaves Explode</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/does-microwaves-kill-botulism/" title="Does Microwaves Kill Botulism" data-wpel-link="internal">Does Microwaves Kill Botulism</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/do-microwaves-destroy-nutrients/" title="Quick Answer: Do Microwaves Destroy Nutrients" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Do Microwaves Destroy Nutrients</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/are-ceramic-microwaves-better/" title="Question: Are Ceramic Microwaves Better" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: Are Ceramic Microwaves Better</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/do-microwaves-penetrate-ceramic/" title="Question: Do Microwaves Penetrate Ceramic" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: Do Microwaves Penetrate Ceramic</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/why-are-microwaves-so-loud/" title="Why Are Microwaves So Loud" data-wpel-link="internal">Why Are Microwaves So Loud</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/do-microwaves-explode-when-empty/" title="Do Microwaves Explode When Empty" data-wpel-link="internal">Do Microwaves Explode When Empty</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/where-to-find-cheap-microwaves/" title="Quick Answer: Where To Find Cheap Microwaves" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Where To Find Cheap Microwaves</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/what-are-the-disadvantages-of-microwaves/" title="Question: What Are The Disadvantages Of Microwaves" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: What Are The Disadvantages Of Microwaves</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/can-you-get-cancer-from-microwaves/" title="Quick Answer: Can You Get Cancer From Microwaves" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Can You Get Cancer From Microwaves</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/are-flatbed-microwaves-better-than-turntable/" title="Quick Answer: Are Flatbed Microwaves Better Than Turntable" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Are Flatbed Microwaves Better Than Turntable</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/why-do-microwaves-heat-up-plates/" title="Quick Answer: Why Do Microwaves Heat Up Plates" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Why Do Microwaves Heat Up Plates</a></li></ol></div><div class='code-block code-block-5' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div class="outbrain-tm" id="86299-16"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=16" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=16" defer></script></div></div> <!-- AI CONTENT END 3 --> 	]]></content:encoded>
<guid isPermaLink="false">6271e443e77ff</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 02:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.seniorcareto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/senior-microwaves-faqs.jpg" /></item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Best Cheap Gaming Laptops for Fallout 4 Under $500 - Seniorcareto]]></title>
<link>https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/11/best-cheap-gaming-laptops-for-fallout-4-under-500/</link>
<description><![CDATA[Table of Contents Our Picks of best cheap cheap gaming laptops for Fallout 4 under $500 1.Acer Aspire 5 “A powerful $500 gaming laptop” 2.Lenovo IdeaPad 330 “The high quality and value of a $500 gaming laptop” 3.Dell Inspiron 15 5575 “Outstanding display and high-performance processor” Conclusion This is a cold and honest truth: you&hellip; &lt;a class=&quot;more-link&quot; href=&quot;http://afru.shop/hello-world/&quot;&gt;Continue reading &lt;span class=&quot;screen-reader-text&quot;&gt;Hello world!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[  		<div id="ez-toc-container" class="ez-toc-v2_0_19 counter-hierarchy counter-decimal ez-toc-grey"> <div class="ez-toc-title-container"> <p class="ez-toc-title">Table of Contents</p> <span class="ez-toc-title-toggle"><a class="ez-toc-pull-right ez-toc-btn ez-toc-btn-xs ez-toc-btn-default ez-toc-toggle" style="display: none;"><i class="ez-toc-glyphicon ez-toc-icon-toggle"></i></a></span></div> <nav><ul class="ez-toc-list ez-toc-list-level-1"><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-1" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/11/best-cheap-gaming-laptops-for-fallout-4-under-500/#Our_Picks_of_best_cheap_cheap_gaming_laptops_for_Fallout_4_under_500" title="Our Picks of best cheap cheap gaming laptops for Fallout 4 under $500">Our Picks of best cheap cheap gaming laptops for Fallout 4 under $500</a><ul class="ez-toc-list-level-3"><li class="ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-2" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/11/best-cheap-gaming-laptops-for-fallout-4-under-500/#1Acer_Aspire_5_A_powerful_500_gaming_laptop" title="1.Acer Aspire 5 “A powerful $500 gaming laptop”">1.Acer Aspire 5 “A powerful $500 gaming laptop”</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-3" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/11/best-cheap-gaming-laptops-for-fallout-4-under-500/#2Lenovo_IdeaPad_330_The_high_quality_and_value_of_a_500_gaming_laptop" title="2.Lenovo IdeaPad 330 “The high quality and value of a $500 gaming laptop”">2.Lenovo IdeaPad 330 “The high quality and value of a $500 gaming laptop”</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-4" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/11/best-cheap-gaming-laptops-for-fallout-4-under-500/#3Dell_Inspiron_15_5575_Outstanding_display_and_high-performance_processor" title="3.Dell Inspiron 15 5575 “Outstanding display and high-performance processor”">3.Dell Inspiron 15 5575 “Outstanding display and high-performance processor”</a></li></ul></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-5" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/11/best-cheap-gaming-laptops-for-fallout-4-under-500/#Conclusion" title="Conclusion">Conclusion</a></li></ul></nav></div>  <p>This is a cold and honest truth: you won’t find a great gaming <strong><a href="https://www.minilaptops.org/best-gaming-laptops-for-fallout-4-under-1200/" data-wpel-link="exclude">laptops for fallout 4 </a></strong>under $500. If you need a more powerful game console and it costs no more than $500, then it is better to buy a gaming desktop (please check this $500 gaming PC version). However, if you absolutely need a laptop that can meet your gaming needs well, then you will need to spend some extra money. (For higher performance options, check out our article “The Best Gaming Laptops Under $1,000.”)</p><div class='code-block code-block-4' style='margin: 8px 0; clear: both;'> <div id="rc-widget-17a600" data-rc-widget data-widget-host="habitat" data-endpoint="//trends.revcontent.com" data-widget-id="269417"></div> <script type="text/javascript" src="https://assets.revcontent.com/master/delivery.js" defer="defer"></script> </div>     <p>However, if you are a casual gamer, or mainly play non-demand games, then you should be able to purchase a $500 gaming laptop.</p><div class='code-block code-block-1' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-19"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=19" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=19" defer></script></div></div>     <p>In this price range, you can still find a budget-friendly laptop that allows you to play League of Legends, Counter-Strike, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fallout_4" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer">Fallout 4</a>, Global Offensive, Dota 2, <a href="https://www.minecraft.net/en-us/" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer">Minecraft</a>, Hearthstone and other games.</p><div class='code-block code-block-2' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-28"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=28" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=28" defer></script></div></div>     <p>Therefore, if you need a gaming laptop that costs less than $500 and cannot use a desktop computer, then the following options are your best choice.</p><div class='code-block code-block-3' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-2"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=2" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=2" defer></script></div></div>     <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Our_Picks_of_best_cheap_cheap_gaming_laptops_for_Fallout_4_under_500"></span>Our Picks of best cheap cheap gaming laptops for Fallout 4 under $500<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="1Acer_Aspire_5_A_powerful_500_gaming_laptop"></span>1.Acer Aspire 5<br>“A powerful $500 gaming laptop”<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="954" height="603" src="data:image/svg+xml,%3Csvg%20xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2000/svg'%20viewBox='0%200%20954%20603'%3E%3C/svg%3E" alt="" class="wp-image-142" data-lazy- data-lazy- data-lazy-src="https://www.seniorcare2share.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/Acer-Aspire-5.jpg" /><noscript><img loading="lazy" width="954" height="603" src="https://www.seniorcare2share.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/Acer-Aspire-5.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-142"   /></noscript></figure></div>    <ul><li>AMD Ryzen 3 3200U dual-core processor</li><li>15.6-inch Full HD (1920 x 1080) widescreen</li><li>1 USB 3.1 Gen 1 port, 2 USB 2.0 ports and 1 HDMI</li><li>802.11ac Wi-Fi; backlit keyboard; up to 7.5 hours</li><li>Windows 10 is in S mode. Maximum power</li></ul>    <p><strong>Pros</strong><br>CPU is great for handling multiple tasks<br>Fashion worthy machine<br><strong>Cons</strong><br>battery is low<br>Wide viewing angle poor quality</p>    <p>Generally, compared with other Acer machines, Acer Aspire 5 is a visible upgrade. Acer’s logo is positioned in a series of waves on the plastic chassis. You can find a sturdy hinge in this Acer product, which will allow you to completely fold the Acer Aspire 5 back to the display parallel to the platform.</p>    <p>This Acer is beautifully decorated and equipped with a dedicated keyboard, including a numeric keypad. This keyword has a refreshing matte effect. This Acer machine is equipped with one of the top audio speakers, and the sound is loud enough to fill the entire room with your favorite pure sound. However, this sound is not accurate. The features of this laptop are very suitable for game lovers.</p>    <p>This metal case created by Acer always brings a higher texture. Whether at home or in the office, carrying this Acer machine with you can inspire confidence, thanks to its sturdy construction. The hinges of this Acer laptop are very clean, allowing the display to stay in place during use.</p>    <p>Considering the relative thickness of this Acer product, when you compare it with other thin and light notebooks today, you have every reason to expect strong online connectivity. The battery life won’t even bother you. The model can be used for a few hours on average. Like this, normal browsing, listening to tracks, and office work, you are expected to consume 6 to 8 hours of battery. You can use this laptop for gaming purposes.</p>    <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="2Lenovo_IdeaPad_330_The_high_quality_and_value_of_a_500_gaming_laptop"></span>2.Lenovo IdeaPad 330<br>“The high quality and value of a $500 gaming laptop”<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="641" src="data:image/svg+xml,%3Csvg%20xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2000/svg'%20viewBox='0%200%201024%20641'%3E%3C/svg%3E" alt="" class="wp-image-143" data-lazy- data-lazy- data-lazy-src="https://www.seniorcare2share.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/Lenovo-IdeaPad-330-1024x641.jpg" /><noscript><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="641" src="https://www.seniorcare2share.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/Lenovo-IdeaPad-330-1024x641.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-143"   /></noscript></figure></div>    <ul><li>Lenovo Ideapad 330 15.6′ Anti-Glare HD Premium Edition</li><li>Lenovo Ideapad 330 15.6″ Anti-Glare HD Premium Edition</li><li>Memory: 8GB DDR4 RAM, storage: 256GB SSD</li><li>The seventh generation AMD A9-9425 processor </li><li>6-inch HD (1366×768) non-touch anti-glare LED</li><li>It comes with a coral red case, Intel wireless</li><li>Windows 10 Home Edition 64-bit-family, student,</li></ul>    <p><strong>Pros</strong><br>Powerful multitasking capabilities<br>Lightweight plastic structure design<br><strong>Cons</strong><br>Poor battery performance<br>The quality of the speakers is impressive</p>    <p>Lenovo IdeaPad 330 is a well-designed high-performance portable notebook computer. The cover of the laptop is made of polished aluminum. This is why the Lenovo IdeaPad 330 looks very premium. In addition, it is very strong and can be transported with one hand without squeaking.</p>    <p>The best display cover also includes aluminum. Due to the thin bezels, certain display covers can easily bend or twist. However, when you just open or close the laptop, its lid does not really twist or bend.</p>    <p>Usually, after removing the bottom cover, the user can clean the internal parts or perform some light maintenance work. You will find a ClickPad in this Lenovo product to replace the mouse. It sits firmly in its position and allows precise movement of the cursor. The fingertips can easily slide across the pad, which is usually why drag and drop does not actually pose any challenges.</p>    <p>Whether you want to use it to the lower left corner or the lower right corner, ClickPad will not have any trouble in the recognition input process. The IdeaPad 330S can choose between a full HD IPS panel (using the resolution associated with 1920 x 1080). In addition, you will also find HD TN panels with a resolution of 1366 x 768.</p>    <p>A 1TB hard drive can provide you with enough space for retail storage of important games and other files. Even under normal circumstances, the appearance of the device cannot be ignored. It has a strong, gorgeous plastic appearance, and has excellent gambling and other functions.</p>    <p>Lenovo has successfully achieved a lasting combination of performance and creativity. Excellent usability, power-driven performance and the most basic ergonomics make this portable computer a one-stop shop, and it is undoubtedly the most effective device for gambling portable computers under $500.</p>    <p>The quality of music may have been improved, and if you don’t wear headphones, you cannot experience the experience of watching movies or listening to specific songs. Battery life is because there is not much surprising average battery performance.</p>    <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="3Dell_Inspiron_15_5575_Outstanding_display_and_high-performance_processor"></span>3.Dell Inspiron 15 5575<br>“Outstanding display and high-performance processor”<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="617" src="data:image/svg+xml,%3Csvg%20xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2000/svg'%20viewBox='0%200%201024%20617'%3E%3C/svg%3E" alt="" class="wp-image-144" data-lazy- data-lazy- data-lazy-src="https://www.seniorcare2share.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/Dell-Inspiron-15-5575-1024x617.jpg" /><noscript><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="617" src="https://www.seniorcare2share.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/Dell-Inspiron-15-5575-1024x617.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-144"   /></noscript></figure></div>    <ul><li>Dell i5575-A217SLV-PUS Inspiron 15 5575-</li><li>Amd Ryzen 5 2500U mobile processor with Radeon</li><li>8GB 2400MHz DDR4 [32GB], (additional memory sold</li><li>1 TB 5400 RPM SATA, the tray is loaded into the DVD drive</li><li>15.6-inch FHD (1920 x 1080) anti-glare</li><li>increase productivity. Windows 10 is best for</li></ul>    <p><br><strong>Pros<br></strong>GPU is great<br>High-performance processor<br>Excellent display<br><strong>Cons</strong><br>SSD Hard not added<br>Low battery life<br>Backlit keyboard is missing</p>    <p>This Dell system provides you with a newly designed 15.6-inch Full HD display, and is carefully decorated with 1920 x 1080 resolution. It also has anti-glare technology. By injecting anti-glare technology into the computer, your eyes will not be hurt at all. Therefore, you can freely play your favorite games for a long time without blinking.</p>    <p>This model is light, only 4.7 pounds. This weight is ideal for travelers who also need to travel many times and look for a portable computer to carry the computer. The central processing unit of this notebook computer will be used in conjunction with 8GB RAM, which is ideal for processing large numbers of abstracts at the same time.</p>    <p>This Dell laptop will be equipped with a 1TB hard drive, enough for individuals to maintain almost all game data and files. However, this Dell model does not have a backlit keyboard.</p>    <p>This Dell machine is equipped with a dedicated numeric keyboard, usually with an excellent space bar on the keyboard, and a single key is easy to press. Graphics on Dell computers are usually supported by AMD Radeon Vega 8 GPUs. You may not have heard of this particular graphics card. However, this is one of the particularly powerful and outstanding graphics cards in this series of notebooks. It can provide you with a good experience, allowing you to handle any great game with normal game settings. The Dell i5575 machine pumps water during 4 to 6 hours of regular work and usually rests during game hours.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Conclusion"></span>Conclusion<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p>With the <strong>best gaming laptops for fallout 4</strong>  in this list that cost less than $500, make sure the laptops are the most suitable and have the best gaming experience of your life!</p>    <p>It is recommended to let us know which one you chose in the comments below and share this article with your friends on social media.</p> <div class="related-posts"><h6>Related Posts</h6><ol><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-a-cheap-gaming-pc-worth-it/" title="Is A Cheap Gaming Pc Worth It" data-wpel-link="internal">Is A Cheap Gaming Pc Worth It</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/can-hardiebacker-500-be-used-on-floors-under-ceramic-tile/" title="Can Hardiebacker 500 Be Used On Floors Under Ceramic Tile" data-wpel-link="internal">Can Hardiebacker 500 Be Used On Floors Under Ceramic Tile</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/do-seniors-who-make-under-500-need-to-file-taxes/" title="Do Seniors Who Make Under 500 Need To File Taxes" data-wpel-link="internal">Do Seniors Who Make Under 500 Need To File Taxes</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/do-laptops-have-displayport/" title="Quick Answer: Do Laptops Have Displayport" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Do Laptops Have Displayport</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/are-all-laptops-16-9/" title="Question: Are All Laptops 16 9" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: Are All Laptops 16 9</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/why-do-laptops-use-16-10/" title="Question: Why Do Laptops Use 16 10" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: Why Do Laptops Use 16 10</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-1080p-gaming-bad/" title="Quick Answer: Is 1080P Gaming Bad" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Is 1080P Gaming Bad</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/does-the-rice-trick-work-for-laptops/" title="Quick Answer: Does The Rice Trick Work For Laptops" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Does The Rice Trick Work For Laptops</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-make-diy-pen-for-laptops/" title="How To Make Diy Pen For Laptops" data-wpel-link="internal">How To Make Diy Pen For Laptops</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/who-has-senior-citizen-discounts-on-laptops/" title="Quick Answer: Who Has Senior Citizen Discounts On Laptops" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Who Has Senior Citizen Discounts On Laptops</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/can-pyrex-handle-500-degrees/" title="Question: Can Pyrex Handle 500 Degrees" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: Can Pyrex Handle 500 Degrees</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-500-a-perfect-cube/" title="Question: Is 500 A Perfect Cube" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: Is 500 A Perfect Cube</a></li></ol></div><div class='code-block code-block-5' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div class="outbrain-tm" id="86299-16"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=16" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=16" defer></script></div></div> <!-- AI CONTENT END 2 --> 	]]></content:encoded>
<guid isPermaLink="false">6271e443e80cd</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 02:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.seniorcareto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/11/Best-Cheap-Gaming-Laptops-for-Fallout-4-Under-500.jpg" /></item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[What is the best double jogger stroller for buy? - Seniorcareto]]></title>
<link>https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/08/what-is-the-best-double-jogger-stroller-for-buy/</link>
<description><![CDATA[When we gave birth to our first child, Ellis, we bought Baby Jogger City Mini. He has been 19 months old and I cherish it very much. We live on the first floor in London, so I need a light carriage, which is difficult to carry everywhere. City Mini checked all containers. When I got&hellip; &lt;a class=&quot;more-link&quot; href=&quot;http://afru.shop/hello-world/&quot;&gt;Continue reading &lt;span class=&quot;screen-reader-text&quot;&gt;Hello world!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[  		 <p>When we gave birth to our first child, Ellis, we bought Baby Jogger City Mini. </p>    <p>He has been 19 months old and I cherish it very much.</p><div class='code-block code-block-4' style='margin: 8px 0; clear: both;'> <div id="rc-widget-17a600" data-rc-widget data-widget-host="habitat" data-endpoint="//trends.revcontent.com" data-widget-id="269417"></div> <script type="text/javascript" src="https://assets.revcontent.com/master/delivery.js" defer="defer"></script> </div>     <p>We live on the first floor in London, so I need a light carriage, which is difficult to carry everywhere. </p><div class='code-block code-block-1' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-19"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=19" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=19" defer></script></div></div>     <p>City Mini checked all containers. When I got the second smallest seat, 15 months later, it seemed easy to decide to get a dual format-one seat after another.</p><div class='code-block code-block-2' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-28"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=28" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=28" defer></script></div></div>     <p></p><div class='code-block code-block-3' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-2"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=2" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=2" defer></script></div></div>     <p>The <a href="https://www.babyjogger.com/en-US/city-mini%3Csup%3E%C2%AE%3C-sup%3E-2-double-bj-city-mini-2-double--1" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer">City Mini Double Stroller</a> has two adjacent Surrey seats. </p>    <p>Nevertheless, it is really minimized at 76 cm wide and can be used in open spaces through most standard entrance passages.</p>    <p></p>    <p>The incredible thing about the Double Stroller City Mini is that it is very lightweight for the Double Stroller.</p>    <p> It weighs only 11.8 kg, so it is not a big choice for me to choose to transport the entire staircase to our horizontal position.</p>    <p></p>    <p>One disadvantage of this carriage is that the Double Stroller City Mini and City Mini GT Double are currently not suitable for any newborn babies.</p>    <p> So if you are looking for a movement, then sadly at this point, this is not the bracket you want.</p>    <p></p>    <p>If you are the parent of twins and want to run with your children, <a href="https://www.ponfish.com/best-double-jogging-stroller-under-300/" data-wpel-link="exclude">a double jogging stroller is the best choice</a>.</p>    <p> Since they have become the main choice for babies, they have multiple benefits.</p>    <p></p>    <h2>The benefits of a double jogging stroller:</h2>    <ul><li>You will be able to run at the same speed</li><li>These strollers have extra storage space</li><li>Useful on the road of sacky</li><li>You can spend quality time with your children</li><li>You can use it while running and walking</li></ul>    <p></p>    <h2>The following are the best twin jogging strollers:</h2>    <ul><li>Jogger 2016 Summit X3</li><li>Jogger 2015 City Selection</li></ul>    <p>There are many double jogging strollers on the market, whether it is all terrain, jogging or parasols, you need your child.</p>    <p>Most side-by-side strollers can only accommodate one infant car seat, so you must bypass these brands.</p>    <p> What are your options? Explore the top stroller suitable for twins. The twins can accommodate two infant car seats, some with multiple seats. </p>    <p>Price points range from ultra-budget to high-end luxury goods. </p>    <p>You can check the basics based on consumer reviews, professional guides, blog commenters, and personal experience. </p>    <p>You can also check twin stroller reviews for twin babies. And choose the best double stroller for twin babies.</p>    <p></p>    <p>The best double jogging cart is a question, but before answering this question, you should know how the type of double jogging cart is better and how to choose it. </p>    <p>If you have two children and you want to control it as a stroller, you can buy a double stroller. </p>    <p>The choice of a double jogging stroller is not more difficult than a single stroller, because both babies are in a double jogging stroller, and the most common problem is that it is comfortable for a single ride. </p>    <p>If you want to know all the criteria and choose the tips for a double stroller, you can check out the double stroller.</p> <div class="related-posts"><h6>Related Posts</h6><ol><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-jogging-bad-for-seniors/" title="Quick Answer: Is Jogging Bad For Seniors" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Is Jogging Bad For Seniors</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-make-a-diaper-stroller/" title="Quick Answer: How To Make A Diaper Stroller" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: How To Make A Diaper Stroller</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/should-i-buy-a-double-boiler-for-diy-e-juice/" title="Quick Answer: Should I Buy A Double Boiler For Diy E Juice" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Should I Buy A Double Boiler For Diy E Juice</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-does-apple-watch-count-steps-when-pushing-a-stroller/" title="Quick Answer: How Does Apple Watch Count Steps When Pushing A Stroller" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: How Does Apple Watch Count Steps When Pushing A Stroller</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/do-you-double-cooking-time-when-you-double-the-recipe/" title="Do You Double Cooking Time When You Double The Recipe" data-wpel-link="internal">Do You Double Cooking Time When You Double The Recipe</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-double-rainbow-rare/" title="Question: Is Double Rainbow Rare" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: Is Double Rainbow Rare</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/do-diamonds-have-double-bonds/" title="Quick Answer: Do Diamonds Have Double Bonds" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Do Diamonds Have Double Bonds</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/what-is-double-coat-plaster/" title="Question: What Is Double Coat Plaster" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: What Is Double Coat Plaster</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/what-does-double-butted-mean/" title="What Does Double Butted Mean" data-wpel-link="internal">What Does Double Butted Mean</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/does-dough-double-in-size/" title="Quick Answer: Does Dough Double In Size" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Does Dough Double In Size</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-100000-double-rubs-meaningless/" title="Is 100000 Double Rubs Meaningless" data-wpel-link="internal">Is 100000 Double Rubs Meaningless</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-a-double-rainbow-rare/" title="Is A Double Rainbow Rare" data-wpel-link="internal">Is A Double Rainbow Rare</a></li></ol></div><div class='code-block code-block-5' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div class="outbrain-tm" id="86299-16"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=16" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=16" defer></script></div></div> <!-- AI CONTENT END 2 --> 	]]></content:encoded>
<guid isPermaLink="false">6271e443e844a</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 02:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.seniorcareto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/08/What-is-the-best-double-jogger-stroller-for-buy.jpg" /></item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Is The Mintlyfe Patch Legit? - Seniorcareto]]></title>
<link>https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/08/is-the-mintlyfe-patch-legit/</link>
<description><![CDATA[Table of Contents 4.8 million views from a company I’ve never heard of: Purchase time: Actual use: 6 weeks update: Q-How do you use it? Q-Will it disappear quickly? Q-Can you fall asleep? Final thoughts – overall rating 9.4/10 This article is from internet, and just for reference. And please refer to the professional experts&hellip; &lt;a class=&quot;more-link&quot; href=&quot;http://afru.shop/hello-world/&quot;&gt;Continue reading &lt;span class=&quot;screen-reader-text&quot;&gt;Hello world!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[  		<div id="ez-toc-container" class="ez-toc-v2_0_19 counter-hierarchy counter-decimal ez-toc-grey"> <div class="ez-toc-title-container"> <p class="ez-toc-title">Table of Contents</p> <span class="ez-toc-title-toggle"><a class="ez-toc-pull-right ez-toc-btn ez-toc-btn-xs ez-toc-btn-default ez-toc-toggle" style="display: none;"><i class="ez-toc-glyphicon ez-toc-icon-toggle"></i></a></span></div> <nav><ul class="ez-toc-list ez-toc-list-level-1"><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-1" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/08/is-the-mintlyfe-patch-legit/#48_million_views_from_a_company_Ive_never_heard_of" title="4.8 million views from a company I’ve never heard of:">4.8 million views from a company I’ve never heard of:</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-2" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/08/is-the-mintlyfe-patch-legit/#Purchase_time" title="Purchase time:">Purchase time:</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-3" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/08/is-the-mintlyfe-patch-legit/#Actual_use" title="Actual use:">Actual use:</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-4" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/08/is-the-mintlyfe-patch-legit/#6_weeks_update" title="6 weeks update:">6 weeks update:</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-5" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/08/is-the-mintlyfe-patch-legit/#Q-How_do_you_use_it" title="Q-How do you use it?">Q-How do you use it?</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-6" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/08/is-the-mintlyfe-patch-legit/#Q-Will_it_disappear_quickly" title="Q-Will it disappear quickly?">Q-Will it disappear quickly?</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-7" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/08/is-the-mintlyfe-patch-legit/#Q-Can_you_fall_asleep" title="Q-Can you fall asleep?">Q-Can you fall asleep?</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-8" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/08/is-the-mintlyfe-patch-legit/#Final_thoughts_-_overall_rating_9410" title="Final thoughts – overall rating 9.4/10">Final thoughts – overall rating 9.4/10</a></li></ul></nav></div>  <p><em><strong>This article is from internet, and just for reference. And please refer to the professional experts or doctors</strong></em></p><div class='code-block code-block-4' style='margin: 8px 0; clear: both;'> <div id="rc-widget-17a600" data-rc-widget data-widget-host="habitat" data-endpoint="//trends.revcontent.com" data-widget-id="269417"></div> <script type="text/javascript" src="https://assets.revcontent.com/master/delivery.js" defer="defer"></script> </div>     <p>If you have visited Facebook recently, <a href="https://www.ponfish.com/do-mintlyfe-patches-work/" data-wpel-link="exclude">you may have seen an ad for Mintlyfe Patch</a>. The abdomen-sized peppermint extract uses the conductivity of sophorosides and transdermal technology to promote weight loss and fat removal. Each patch contains a cocktail of 56 ingredients, including mint, Korean ginseng and capsaicin. These ingredients are regarded as the key to quickly and safely get rid of fat accumulation and cellulite in the “fluffy” area. A big promise was made, so I decided to test…</p><div class='code-block code-block-1' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-19"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=19" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=19" defer></script></div></div>     <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="48_million_views_from_a_company_Ive_never_heard_of"></span>4.8 million views from a company I’ve never heard of:<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p>I quickly found Mysticform LLC, the company behind the viral Facebook campaign. Korean health product manufacturer, registered in California, and registered with Dr. E. Kojima. After a quick search, I can find articles about the company, its owners and its website. They are real, they have received rave reviews, but the only way to really know is to use it.</p><div class='code-block code-block-2' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-28"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=28" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=28" defer></script></div></div>     <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Purchase_time"></span>Purchase time:<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p><br>I ordered 60 patches, 20 of which are for friends and family because they have a large volume discount. Delivery is fast. The box is large compared to the size of the patch, but I really wanted to try it, so I tore it open in a few seconds.</p><div class='code-block code-block-3' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-2"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=2" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=2" defer></script></div></div>     <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Actual_use"></span>Actual use:<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p>When I put them on for the first time, I felt very nervous because they were smaller than those shown on their website. The size of each pad is about 10 inches and cannot cover my entire lower abdomen. The glue stick quickly made up for this, and I decided to go to work as usual. Dress carefully.</p>    <p>They recommend keeping it for about 6-8 hours, so I expect to start to feel the effect at noon. However, a slight burning sensation can be felt in less than 30 minutes. Not a pain, but comparable to Vicks Vaporub. I feel energetic-probably because it contains caffeine and capsaicin. I even choose not to eat lunch. Things I almost never do.</p>    <p>Later that day, the feeling of burning intensified. The whole process is equivalent to long-term aerobic exercise. It was very hot that day, so when it was time to remove the patch, I sweated a lot. The glue stick means I will encounter a lot of resistance when removing it. I recommend tearing it off slowly, just like when waxing.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="6_weeks_update"></span>6 weeks update:<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p>After using the patch for six weeks, I noticed a significant reduction in <a href="https://www.webmd.com/diet/features/the-truth-about-belly-fat" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer">belly fat</a>. Even more impressive is that my waist lost a total of about an inch. Now, I use these patches every other day, and when I use it, I feel more dynamic in my work.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Q-How_do_you_use_it"></span>Q-How do you use it?<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p><br>I have seen the best results of alternate application of the patch for 6 to 8 hours a day (one rest day). I did not encounter any problems during the mission, but this may mean that sweat will accumulate faster on hot days.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Q-Will_it_disappear_quickly"></span>Q-Will it disappear quickly?<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p>Not at all, because it is made of water-based adhesive non-woven fabric. Consider how the band-aid will stick to the skin, and then multiply the strength by ten times to make it waterproof. This is my experience, it is very sticky, unless you want to reuse it.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Q-Can_you_fall_asleep"></span>Q-Can you fall asleep?<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p>Although there is nothing to say that you cannot turn on the patch to sleep, I recommend that you wear it when you are awake. Activities not only help increase the fat burning effect of the patch, but also help you track time.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Final_thoughts_-_overall_rating_9410"></span>Final thoughts – overall rating 9.4/10<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p>Pros-I can definitely understand the hype surrounding it. Really effective, use all natural ingredients carefully and carefully. It is ideal for those who want to lose weight quickly and can withstand minor burns.</p>    <p>Not good-only for US customers. It is not recommended to use it while sleeping. It can be annoying when running or in the gym.</p>    <p>Important update-During my research, I found many fakes of Mintlyfe WonderPatch. All products are listed at similar prices, but unsafe copies are shipped, and sometimes not even shipped at all-this is a complaint I have seen on many forums. After asking their team, they confirmed that the only official link available for WonderPatch is the link below because they are not listed in the store or Amazon.</p>    <p>Final note-I have reviewed my share of health products. Therefore, I think I have a wealth of experience in buying experience. Nevertheless, I am happy to say that even if I have some small complaints about this, I cannot think of a compelling reason not to try.</p> <div class="related-posts"><h6>Related Posts</h6><ol><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-the-senior-citizens-league-legit/" title="Question: Is The Senior Citizens League Legit" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: Is The Senior Citizens League Legit</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-topcoat-f11-legit/" title="Quick Answer: Is Topcoat F11 Legit" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Is Topcoat F11 Legit</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-ceramic-pro-legit/" title="Is Ceramic Pro Legit" data-wpel-link="internal">Is Ceramic Pro Legit</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-diy-degree-legit/" title="Is Diy Degree Legit" data-wpel-link="internal">Is Diy Degree Legit</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-diy-tax-legit/" title="Is Diy Tax Legit" data-wpel-link="internal">Is Diy Tax Legit</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-handmade-writing-legit/" title="Question: Is Handmade Writing Legit" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: Is Handmade Writing Legit</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-the-senior-security-alliance-a-legit-organization/" title="Is The Senior Security Alliance A Legit Organization" data-wpel-link="internal">Is The Senior Security Alliance A Legit Organization</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-clean-the-bathroom-quickly/" title="Question: How To Clean The Bathroom Quickly" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: How To Clean The Bathroom Quickly</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-diy-make-a-legit-craft/" title="Quick Answer: How To Diy Make A Legit Craft" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: How To Diy Make A Legit Craft</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/are-senior-final-expense-benefits-mailings-legit/" title="Question: Are Senior Final Expense Benefits Mailings Legit" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: Are Senior Final Expense Benefits Mailings Legit</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-for-senior-care-a-legit-website/" title="Is For Senior Care A Legit Website" data-wpel-link="internal">Is For Senior Care A Legit Website</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/why-did-the-plague-spread-so-quickly/" title="Why Did The Plague Spread So Quickly" data-wpel-link="internal">Why Did The Plague Spread So Quickly</a></li></ol></div><div class='code-block code-block-5' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div class="outbrain-tm" id="86299-16"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=16" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=16" defer></script></div></div> <!-- AI CONTENT END 2 --> 	]]></content:encoded>
<guid isPermaLink="false">6271e443e88b7</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 02:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.seniorcareto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/08/Is-The-Mintlyfe-Patch-Legit.jpg" /></item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Breastfeeding and the Working Moms - Seniorcareto]]></title>
<link>https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/08/breastfeeding-and-the-working-moms/</link>
<description><![CDATA[Can I continue breastfeeding after I return to work? Yes, you can. If you live in a nearby workplace or at a daycare center on site or nearby, you can take a break from nursing time to feed your baby. If this is not possible, there are two options: Option 1: You can use a&hellip; &lt;a class=&quot;more-link&quot; href=&quot;http://afru.shop/hello-world/&quot;&gt;Continue reading &lt;span class=&quot;screen-reader-text&quot;&gt;Hello world!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[  		 <h2>Can I continue breastfeeding after I return to work?</h2>    <p><br>Yes, you can. If you live in a nearby workplace or at a daycare center on site or nearby, you can take a break from nursing time to feed your baby. If this is not possible, there are two options:</p>    <p>Option 1: You can use a high-quality electric breast pump to replenish milk during working days to maintain milk supply. Your child’s nanny can give your baby a bottle of <a href="https://www.ponfish.com/tips-for-working-moms-with-breastfeeding/" data-wpel-link="exclude">breast milk</a> that you express. (If you can’t produce enough milk, you can also add formula milk.) You can still breastfeed your baby whenever you are not going to work.</p><div class='code-block code-block-4' style='margin: 8px 0; clear: both;'> <div id="rc-widget-17a600" data-rc-widget data-widget-host="habitat" data-endpoint="//trends.revcontent.com" data-widget-id="269417"></div> <script type="text/javascript" src="https://assets.revcontent.com/master/delivery.js" defer="defer"></script> </div>     <h2>Watch this video “Breastfeeding Tips for the Working Mom”(6 mins 36 seconds)</h2>    <div class="rll-youtube-player" data-src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/I9ZKtRqbQds" data-id="I9ZKtRqbQds" data-query=""></div><noscript><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/I9ZKtRqbQds" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></noscript>    <p>The Protected and Affordable Care Act (PPACA) of the United States was signed into law in 2010, requiring employers to provide reasonable pumping breaks and private bathrooms (except bathrooms) for moms of babies under 12 months. (Employers with fewer than 50 employees do not have to comply. If they do, it will cause “unnecessary difficulties.”) For more detailed information, please read this US government fact sheet.</p><div class='code-block code-block-1' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-19"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=19" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=19" defer></script></div></div>     <p>Option 2: If you can’t or don’t want to pump water at work, you can gradually use formula milk at home instead of day feeding, but continue nursing at night and in the morning. But remember, if you do not breastfeed or pump during the day, your milk supply will decrease.</p><div class='code-block code-block-2' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-28"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=28" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=28" defer></script></div></div>     <p>I can’t speak for all women, but when I have to put my 8-week-old baby with myself or someone other than my husband, I am indeed full of fear. Do you know that you feel stomach discomfort when something bad happens? Is it like that dripping stomach? This is how I feel every day for a long time.</p><div class='code-block code-block-3' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-2"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=2" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=2" defer></script></div></div>     <p>It’s like my brain and my body just learned something is wrong. Every time, my heart feels pain for them. My brain knows something is missing (my eyes were crying when I typed). My baby disappeared 56 days after giving birth and my body knew it. This feeling, anxiety, and fear are reactions to their leaving my body and emotions, which is definitely a shock to my system.</p>    <p>Even if I knew it was not right, even if everything in me screamed “No!” I went back because I was a breadwinner and an insurance holder. I am precious to my family and our survival, and we cannot live without my income. This is not our choice, not even for a few weeks. But apart from being a breadwinner, I am also a food source for our babies.</p>    <p>I know that you are taking the break to pump water. I know that you eat while pumping or at work, because you will spend time during your lunch break to make sure your baby has lunch tomorrow. I know that every time you stand up and say “I need to pump water now”, you want to know if this is convenient for your colleagues.</p>    <p>I know you will pick up your pump bag and go to a room that hardly meets the legal requirements set by the government. You will hang a sign on the door-warning people not to enter-they will no doubt still enter. Or maybe you cover yourself and pull into the office or cubicle, while others work by your side.</p>    <p>I know you will milk your own milk until you are full. I know you will follow your baby’s eating habits as much as possible. A 6-week-old baby eats often-very, very frequently. I know that sometimes the milk you go home is not enough to feed your baby. I know you will feel defeated.</p>    <p>I also know that these “right to pump break time” are not paid. Maybe your boss asks you to work overtime at all these gas station jobs, and every time you are eliminated, you need to stay longer. This will only increase the time at the end of your already long day, and even longer, until you take that sweet and warm baby home.</p>    <p>I know you will stand up and announce that you need to cheer. You will hear a series of comments from colleagues: “again?” “How long will you do this?” “Are you still weaning?” “Oh, that’s disgusting. “Does this make you feel like a cow?” “You don’t put milk in the employee refrigerator, do you?” “I wish I could take a break like you.”</p>    <p>I know you will feel inside because all you really want to do is the best thing you can do for you and your children. I know you are eager to have lunch with colleagues again. I know that watching your favorite videos on your phone when you are pumping can really help pumping. I know that the close-up video you took can actually hear the baby’s gasp, and they do cry.</p>    <p>I know that a “good <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Breast_pump" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer">pump</a>” deserves a high five and a hug. I know that a colleague who pumps water will become your new job BFF because she got it. I know that when you get home, the last thing to do is pump water. You want that baby to be held in your arms and uzzled into your neck. You want the big round eyes to look up at you, and the tacky smile when they are still locked. I know that pumping is a labor of love. I know that our full-time mom friend doesn’t understand at all.</p>    <p>I know this will make you feel like another microscope at work. “How many minutes did she smoke there?” “How much rest time did she get?” “How long must we let her do this?” “Have her work done?” “Why can’t she just feed formula?” I know. When you spend the night with that cute baby, you worry about your performance the next day at work, but at the same time, you still cherish those quiet moments. Those moments when no one else is around. It’s dark and calm. You can feed your baby and stroke his hair. Don’t think about how to pull yourself together within three hours of the alarm. I know that dry shampoo and pumping water suits are your best new friends.</p>    <p>I know that coffee makes your world go round. I know that hearing “you look tired” becomes mainstream. I know that mastitis, whitening of nipples and vasospasm are the sons of the B word. Between taking advantage of all paid maternity leave and sick babies, you can never miss any work to take care of these diseases. Even if you do miss your job, no one will understand.</p>    <p>I know how it feels to question your professionalism, and I know you are already worried about how they would even take you seriously when your breast milk leaked from your upper abdomen last week, but the next day you cried for no reason, you Reluctantly maintain the job. I know that you are at the end between doing housework and being a mom, doing things and pumping water.</p>    <p>The question “how do we as women engage in occupations and feed babies?” turned a deaf ear. We wanted a solution and they gave us: “Here is a pump and a room. Your employer will not be able to punish you for smoking. They must legally let you do this, but they don’t have to like it, nor No need to provide convenience for you. Now, if you want, you can resume work 42 days after giving birth.”</p> <div class="related-posts"><h6>Related Posts</h6><ol><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/do-new-moms-appreciate-handmade-baby-gifts/" title="Quick Answer: Do New Moms Appreciate Handmade Baby Gifts" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Do New Moms Appreciate Handmade Baby Gifts</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/what-to-make-for-your-moms-birthday-diy/" title="What To Make For Your Moms Birthday Diy" data-wpel-link="internal">What To Make For Your Moms Birthday Diy</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/can-i-use-my-moms-senior-national-park-pass/" title="Quick Answer: Can I Use My Moms Senior National Park Pass" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Can I Use My Moms Senior National Park Pass</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-target-high-school-senior-moms-facebook-ads/" title="How To Target High School Senior Moms Facebook Ads" data-wpel-link="internal">How To Target High School Senior Moms Facebook Ads</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/can-you-pump-concrete/" title="Can You Pump Concrete" data-wpel-link="internal">Can You Pump Concrete</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-sump-pump/" title="Question: How To Sump Pump" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: How To Sump Pump</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/are-nurses-working-class/" title="Are Nurses Working Class" data-wpel-link="internal">Are Nurses Working Class</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-gmail-working-now/" title="Quick Answer: Is Gmail Working Now" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Is Gmail Working Now</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-fresh-milk-better-than-powdered-milk/" title="Question: Is Fresh Milk Better Than Powdered Milk" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: Is Fresh Milk Better Than Powdered Milk</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/what-is-concrete-boom-pump/" title="What Is Concrete Boom Pump" data-wpel-link="internal">What Is Concrete Boom Pump</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/who-installs-a-sump-pump/" title="Quick Answer: Who Installs A Sump Pump" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Who Installs A Sump Pump</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/where-to-install-sump-pump/" title="Question: Where To Install Sump Pump" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: Where To Install Sump Pump</a></li></ol></div><div class='code-block code-block-5' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div class="outbrain-tm" id="86299-16"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=16" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=16" defer></script></div></div> <!-- AI CONTENT END 2 --> 	]]></content:encoded>
<guid isPermaLink="false">6271e443e8c9e</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 02:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.seniorcareto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/08/Breastfeeding-Tips-for-the-Working-Mom.jpg" /></item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[How To Spot Fake Yeezys Boost 700 - Seniorcareto]]></title>
<link>https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/07/how-to-spot-fake-yeezys-boost-700/</link>
<description><![CDATA[Table of Contents Toe suede quality Leather quality 3M material Check grid pattern Sneaker shape Sports heel Yeezy Box Where can Yeezy Boost 700 Wave Runner be authenticated? Are you wondering how to discover the fastest method of Yeezy Boost 700 Wave Runner (OG)? If you don’t mind adding another pair of stylish Yeezy to&hellip; &lt;a class=&quot;more-link&quot; href=&quot;http://afru.shop/hello-world/&quot;&gt;Continue reading &lt;span class=&quot;screen-reader-text&quot;&gt;Hello world!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[  		<div id="ez-toc-container" class="ez-toc-v2_0_19 counter-hierarchy counter-decimal ez-toc-grey"> <div class="ez-toc-title-container"> <p class="ez-toc-title">Table of Contents</p> <span class="ez-toc-title-toggle"><a class="ez-toc-pull-right ez-toc-btn ez-toc-btn-xs ez-toc-btn-default ez-toc-toggle" style="display: none;"><i class="ez-toc-glyphicon ez-toc-icon-toggle"></i></a></span></div> <nav><ul class="ez-toc-list ez-toc-list-level-1"><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-1" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/07/how-to-spot-fake-yeezys-boost-700/#Toe_suede_quality" title="Toe suede quality">Toe suede quality</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-2" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/07/how-to-spot-fake-yeezys-boost-700/#Leather_quality" title="Leather quality">Leather quality</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-3" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/07/how-to-spot-fake-yeezys-boost-700/#3M_material" title="3M material">3M material</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-4" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/07/how-to-spot-fake-yeezys-boost-700/#Check_grid_pattern" title="Check grid pattern">Check grid pattern</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-5" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/07/how-to-spot-fake-yeezys-boost-700/#Sneaker_shape" title="Sneaker shape">Sneaker shape</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-6" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/07/how-to-spot-fake-yeezys-boost-700/#Sports_heel" title="Sports heel">Sports heel</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-7" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/07/how-to-spot-fake-yeezys-boost-700/#Yeezy_Box" title="Yeezy Box">Yeezy Box</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-8" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/07/how-to-spot-fake-yeezys-boost-700/#Where_can_Yeezy_Boost_700_Wave_Runner_be_authenticated" title="Where can Yeezy Boost 700 Wave Runner be authenticated?">Where can Yeezy Boost 700 Wave Runner be authenticated?</a></li></ul></nav></div>  <p>Are you wondering how to discover the fastest method of <a href="https://stockx.com/adidas/yeezy/700" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer">Yeezy Boost 700</a> Wave Runner (OG)?</p><div class='code-block code-block-4' style='margin: 8px 0; clear: both;'> <div id="rc-widget-17a600" data-rc-widget data-widget-host="habitat" data-endpoint="//trends.revcontent.com" data-widget-id="269417"></div> <script type="text/javascript" src="https://assets.revcontent.com/master/delivery.js" defer="defer"></script> </div>     <p>If you don’t mind adding another pair of stylish Yeezy to the spin, you should choose Yeezy Boost 700 OG.</p><div class='code-block code-block-1' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-19"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=19" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=19" defer></script></div></div>     <p>Whether you are a sneaker or not, you want to make sure you know whether you are looking for real or fake Yeezy OG when you buy Yeezy Boost 700 Wave Runner.</p><div class='code-block code-block-2' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-28"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=28" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=28" defer></script></div></div>     <p>That’s why we created this “Final and Real Yeezy 700 OG Comparison Final Guide”, which embeds images that can help you identify counterfeit sneakers and real sneakers.</p><div class='code-block code-block-3' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-2"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=2" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=2" defer></script></div></div>     <p>The best way to identify fake Yeezy Boost 700 OG is to check Wave Runners for major inconsistencies and warn against using a true pair. The most important indicator you should check is the size label, where the style and text can distinguish the true Yeezy 700 Wave Runner version from the duplicate Yeezy 700 Wave Runner version.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Toe_suede_quality"></span>Toe suede quality<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p><br>The suede toe box of the real Yeezy 700 Wave runner is rougher and has a grainy feel. Compared to the fake pair, the fake pair is very smooth and looks really cheap.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Leather_quality"></span>Leather quality<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p><br>Like the toe box, the leather on the real Wave Runners is not completely smooth, and some tumbling, indicating better quality. The pins on the true Yeezy 700s are darker and more embedded.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="3M_material"></span>3M material<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p>Like Jordan and other sports shoes, Yeezy Boost 700 Wave Runner reflects 3m of material on some parts of the website. You can use the flash on your phone to view these contents. In fact, the two circles in the black material are larger than those in the fake and look closer.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Check_grid_pattern"></span>Check grid pattern<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p>The upper design of Yeezy Boost 700 is unique and unique. The actual salary should be darker and the space should be tight so that it looks tight. The pattern of fake 700 will be slightly lighter than the color.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Sneaker_shape"></span>Sneaker shape<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p><br>The shape of fakes is often higher and more lumpy. Wave runners are already bulky shoes, but the fake 700s look even bulkier.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Sports_heel"></span>Sports heel<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p><br>The quality of the heel depends on the texture of the leather and focuses on the mesh area around the heel.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Yeezy_Box"></span>Yeezy Box<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p><br>Most counterfeit goods have different packaging boxes, and the quality of the packaging boxes is usually very poor, more than those in harsh conditions. The front of the Yeezy 700 box may be too small or missing key stickers.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Where_can_Yeezy_Boost_700_Wave_Runner_be_authenticated"></span>Where can Yeezy Boost 700 Wave Runner be authenticated?<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p>If you need help with Yeezy Boost 700 Wave Runner (OG) authentication, we will help you.</p>    <p>All you need to do is send us high-quality pictures of your 700 OG, and we will provide the results to you within 24 to 48 hours. The result will also be accompanied by a report explaining why we think your sneakers are fake or real.</p>    <p>This brings us to the end of the comparison between the<a href="https://www.seniorcare2share.com/2020/07/how-to-detect-fake-adidas-yeezy-boost-750/" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer"> real and fake</a> Yeezy Boost 700 Wave Runner guide. As better and latest comparisons are introduced, we will continue to update this article.</p>    <p>Need our opinion on the authenticity of your product? This is the service we provide.</p> <div class="related-posts"><h6>Related Posts</h6><ol><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-can-you-spot-a-fake-diamond/" title="Question: How Can You Spot A Fake Diamond" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: How Can You Spot A Fake Diamond</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/are-yeezys-handmade/" title="Are Yeezys Handmade" data-wpel-link="internal">Are Yeezys Handmade</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-spot-a-fake-rolex-submariner-ceramic/" title="How To Spot A Fake Rolex Submariner Ceramic" data-wpel-link="internal">How To Spot A Fake Rolex Submariner Ceramic</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-detect-fake-adidas-yeezy-boost-750/" title="Quick Answer: How To Detect Fake Adidas Yeezy Boost 750" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: How To Detect Fake Adidas Yeezy Boost 750</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/who-scored-700-career-goals/" title="Quick Answer: Who Scored 700 Career Goals" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Who Scored 700 Career Goals</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-can-i-make-700-fast/" title="Quick Answer: How Can I Make 700 Fast" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: How Can I Make 700 Fast</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-leaf-spot-contagious/" title="Is Leaf Spot Contagious" data-wpel-link="internal">Is Leaf Spot Contagious</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-powerful-is-a-700-watt-microwave/" title="Quick Answer: How Powerful Is A 700 Watt Microwave" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: How Powerful Is A 700 Watt Microwave</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/can-you-spot-fix-epoxy/" title="Question: Can You Spot Fix Epoxy" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: Can You Spot Fix Epoxy</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-spot-clean-shoes/" title="Quick Answer: How To Spot Clean Shoes" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: How To Spot Clean Shoes</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-spot-clean-upholstery/" title="Question: How To Spot Clean Upholstery" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: How To Spot Clean Upholstery</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/what-is-ceramic-boost/" title="What Is Ceramic Boost" data-wpel-link="internal">What Is Ceramic Boost</a></li></ol></div><div class='code-block code-block-5' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div class="outbrain-tm" id="86299-16"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=16" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=16" defer></script></div></div> <!-- AI CONTENT END 2 --> 	]]></content:encoded>
<guid isPermaLink="false">6271e443e90ea</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 02:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.seniorcareto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/How-To-Spot-Fake-Yeezys-Boost-700.jpg" /></item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[How to detect fake Adidas Yeezy Boost 750? - Seniorcareto]]></title>
<link>https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/07/how-to-detect-fake-adidas-yeezy-boost-750/</link>
<description><![CDATA[If you can’t get a rating for the “Light Gray Yeezy Boost 750” launched on June 11, you may want to snap up a pair on eBay, Craigslist and other sites. Be sure to go out and buy things, but arm yourself as much as possible to avoid eventually getting counterfeit products. The light gray&hellip; &lt;a class=&quot;more-link&quot; href=&quot;http://afru.shop/hello-world/&quot;&gt;Continue reading &lt;span class=&quot;screen-reader-text&quot;&gt;Hello world!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[  		 <p>If you can’t get a rating for the “Light Gray Yeezy Boost 750” launched on June 11, you may want to snap up a pair on eBay, Craigslist and other sites. Be sure to go out and buy things, but arm yourself as much as possible to avoid eventually getting counterfeit products. </p>    <p>The light gray <a href="https://www.flightclub.com/yeezy/boost-750" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer">Yeezy Boost 750s</a> was sold out within a minute after it was released. We turn to brand-certified experts to ensure that counterfeiting is avoided at all costs.</p><div class='code-block code-block-4' style='margin: 8px 0; clear: both;'> <div id="rc-widget-17a600" data-rc-widget data-widget-host="habitat" data-endpoint="//trends.revcontent.com" data-widget-id="269417"></div> <script type="text/javascript" src="https://assets.revcontent.com/master/delivery.js" defer="defer"></script> </div>     <p> Read 7 tips about finding fakes, and then bring a pair of official <a href="https://www.kanyewest.com/" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer">Kanye West</a> dream sneakers highly sought after.</p><div class='code-block code-block-1' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-19"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=19" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=19" defer></script></div></div>     <h2>Here are a few steps to identify the fake Yeezy Boost 750.</h2>    <p>The latest issue of the light gray Yeezy Boost 750s was discontinued on June 11th, which caught the attention of Kanye West fans and sneaker collectors.</p><div class='code-block code-block-2' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-28"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=28" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=28" defer></script></div></div>     <p> These shoes are reminiscent of the hysterics when the Air Jordan was released. In each subsequent release, you will find countless people trying to rate this coveted pair of sneakers.</p><div class='code-block code-block-3' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-2"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=2" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=2" defer></script></div></div>     <p> Therefore, it is not surprising that the light gray Yeezy Boost 750 sold out in a minute (of course, the designer turned by the rapper released this data with pride).</p>    <p><br>Now, the light gray Yeezy Boost 750s is priced on thousands of dollars on eBay. Since the demand for Kanye sneakers always exceeds the available supply, there is reason to believe that Yeezy Boosts are vulnerable to counterfeit goods.</p>    <p> A teenager learned that this path was difficult, when he suggested dating a pair of fake Yeezy Boosts (she found them fake on Twitter!). When fakes are being peddled every moment, how can we ensure that we get the real ones?</p>    <p></p>    <p>We asked Graham Wetzbarger, senior director of RealReal authentication, to help us eliminate counterfeit products. Graham (Graham) has a career of ten years, he is keenly concerned about brand identifiers, and he is sharing his expertise in time with Yeezy Boost resale.</p>    <p> Click to see his must-read tips to discover the fake light gray Yeezy Boost 750 (preferably try your luck).</p>    <p>“Youth Fashion News”: What better details can be easily ignored between fakes and real Yeezys?</p>    <p><br>Graham Wetzbarger: Be sure to check the quality of the suture. Look for excessive or visible glue stains where the sole is attached to the shoe. Shoelaces can usually be used as a giveaway: make sure they are the correct pattern and completed correctly. </p>    <p>Finally, look at the logo and brand mark of the entire shoe. They should be clean, crispy and evenly weighted.</p>    <p>TV: When buying Yeezy’s pair, what materials do we need to prove its authenticity?</p>    <p><br>GW: The manufacturing process of the 750 consists of many complex components. These help to distinguish between genuine and fake shoes. Starting with Boost material: </p>    <p>This proprietary foam is composed of TPU containers that are infused with air and bonded together. If you are familiar with this look and feel, then you will proceed smoothly.</p>    <p>The first thing to consider is the overall quality. Look for alignment issues, material separation, or any other quality issues that do not meet your requirements.</p>    <p>If you find any of these problems, they may be fake.</p>    <p>Next, look at the hole near the toe box. There should be 5 holes in the first row, as shown above, there are only 4 fakes.</p>    <p>Next, look at the pins on the side of the shoe. The stitches should be even and straight. Note that in the fake above, the stitching quality is poor.</p>    <p>Next, look at the stitching on the Velcro of the belt. You won’t see poor quality stitches or threads like the fake above.</p>    <p>Next, look at the internal belt. There should be a small gap between the Velcro and the three flat reinforcements. Note that in the two forgery examples above, the top one is too large, and the bottom one has no gaps at all.</p>    <p>Next, look at the upper seam on the back of the shoe. The seam should be straight up, as shown in the real seam above.</p>    <p>Note that on fakes, the seam moves upward at an acute angle.</p>    <p>Next, see how they stand. They should stand upright and stay in shape. Note that on fakes, they appear to wither and collapse inward.</p>    <p>Next, take a look at the insole. The left-right direction should be opposite to the above direction.</p>    <p>Finally, take a look at the dust bag (if any). The top stitch should have 2 lines. Please note that the fake above has only one line.</p>    <p>TV: What is the retail price of a pair of shoes, and what price should raise the alarm for the resale market?</p>    <p><br>GW: When launched on June 11, the retail price of Yeezy 750 Boost was $350. Currently, any commodity below $1,500 is a red flag in the resale market. </p>    <p>But things often fluctuate, which is why it is important to understand your market and see the comparable [price] between different sellers.</p>    <p>TV: What does the real Yeezy Boost label look like?</p>    <p><br>GW: Boost itself has no tags. You will need to look carefully at the label on the box and compare the style number, PO, artwork number, and even the barcode. Each shoe has an associated label. This information should match the contents on the box.</p>    <p>TV: Are they half the size?</p>    <p><br>GW: Yeezy Boost 750 (gum sole) is available for half size for the first time. It is expected that future releases will also be available in half the size. Light brown and black are only available in full size.</p>    <p>What kind of packaging will the real Yeezy sneakers for TV use?</p>    <p><br>GW: Yeezy Boost 750s is packed in a paper box that is not easy to fold. The new plastic-soled packaging box is very smooth, with diamond-shaped patterns on the packaging of earlier versions.</p>    <p>TV: Any other tips?</p>    <p><br>GW: Whenever you shop, you should buy from a trusted source to ensure authenticity, and have a customer service department that can contact you, and use a secure payment processor.</p>    <p> I can’t tell you how many stories I’ve heard, people order goods online, never get them, and then ruin their credit cards a month later.</p>    <p>In addition, please wait in line [next version]! Get to know the other sports toe caps participating in this release, which may be a very interesting experience. </p>    <p>Nothing is more fascinating than the combination of a sore foot, cold night and onlookers, who wonder what these crazy people are doing outside the Footlocker at 2am.</p> <div class="related-posts"><h6>Related Posts</h6><ol><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-can-i-get-a-free-adidas-sticker/" title="Quick Answer: How Can I Get A Free Adidas Sticker" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: How Can I Get A Free Adidas Sticker</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/can-airport-scanners-detect-money/" title="Can Airport Scanners Detect Money" data-wpel-link="internal">Can Airport Scanners Detect Money</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/can-metal-detectors-detect-knife/" title="Question: Can Metal Detectors Detect Knife" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: Can Metal Detectors Detect Knife</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/can-airport-scanners-detect-pills/" title="Quick Answer: Can Airport Scanners Detect Pills" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Can Airport Scanners Detect Pills</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/can-metal-detectors-detect-drugs/" title="Can Metal Detectors Detect Drugs" data-wpel-link="internal">Can Metal Detectors Detect Drugs</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/where-can-i-metal-detect/" title="Question: Where Can I Metal Detect" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: Where Can I Metal Detect</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/can-metal-detectors-detect-ceramic/" title="Quick Answer: Can Metal Detectors Detect Ceramic" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Can Metal Detectors Detect Ceramic</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/can-airport-scanners-detect-glass/" title="Can Airport Scanners Detect Glass" data-wpel-link="internal">Can Airport Scanners Detect Glass</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/can-airport-scanner-detect-cancer/" title="Can Airport Scanner Detect Cancer" data-wpel-link="internal">Can Airport Scanner Detect Cancer</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/can-airport-scanner-detect-money/" title="Question: Can Airport Scanner Detect Money" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: Can Airport Scanner Detect Money</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-do-you-detect-drowsiness/" title="How Do You Detect Drowsiness" data-wpel-link="internal">How Do You Detect Drowsiness</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/do-observers-detect-crafting-table/" title="Do Observers Detect Crafting Table" data-wpel-link="internal">Do Observers Detect Crafting Table</a></li></ol></div><div class='code-block code-block-5' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div class="outbrain-tm" id="86299-16"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=16" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=16" defer></script></div></div> <!-- AI CONTENT END 2 --> 	]]></content:encoded>
<guid isPermaLink="false">6271e443e952c</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 02:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.seniorcareto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/fake-adidas-yeezy-boost-750.jpg" /></item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[Craft Fair Tips 2020 - Seniorcareto]]></title>
<link>https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/craft-fair-tips/</link>
<description><![CDATA[Table of Contents Watch this video “SELLING AT CRAFT FAIRS | My Top Tips”(22 mins 47 seconds) Supplies: Table Setup: Signage: Price: Categories display: This is a review and some other tips and tricks: What’s new in the artisan world? I am focused on helping you set up the craft exhibition. The appearance is beautiful&hellip; &lt;a class=&quot;more-link&quot; href=&quot;http://afru.shop/hello-world/&quot;&gt;Continue reading &lt;span class=&quot;screen-reader-text&quot;&gt;Hello world!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[  		<div id="ez-toc-container" class="ez-toc-v2_0_19 counter-hierarchy counter-decimal ez-toc-grey"> <div class="ez-toc-title-container"> <p class="ez-toc-title">Table of Contents</p> <span class="ez-toc-title-toggle"><a class="ez-toc-pull-right ez-toc-btn ez-toc-btn-xs ez-toc-btn-default ez-toc-toggle" style="display: none;"><i class="ez-toc-glyphicon ez-toc-icon-toggle"></i></a></span></div> <nav><ul class="ez-toc-list ez-toc-list-level-1"><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-1" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/craft-fair-tips/#Watch_this_video_SELLING_AT_CRAFT_FAIRS_My_Top_Tips22_mins_47_seconds" title="Watch this video “SELLING AT CRAFT FAIRS | My Top Tips”(22 mins 47 seconds)">Watch this video “SELLING AT CRAFT FAIRS | My Top Tips”(22 mins 47 seconds)</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-2" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/craft-fair-tips/#Supplies" title="Supplies:">Supplies:</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-3" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/craft-fair-tips/#Table_Setup" title="Table Setup:">Table Setup:</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-4" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/craft-fair-tips/#Signage" title="Signage:">Signage:</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-5" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/craft-fair-tips/#Price" title="Price:">Price:</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-6" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/craft-fair-tips/#Categories_display" title="Categories display:">Categories display:</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-7" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/craft-fair-tips/#This_is_a_review_and_some_other_tips_and_tricks" title="This is a review and some other tips and tricks:">This is a review and some other tips and tricks:</a></li></ul></nav></div>  <p>What’s new in the artisan world? I am focused on helping you set up the craft exhibition. The appearance is beautiful but not crowded, and the attractive display determines whether the partons will stop or continue walking. I list some important elements and then discuss them in detail.</p><div class='code-block code-block-4' style='margin: 8px 0; clear: both;'> <div id="rc-widget-17a600" data-rc-widget data-widget-host="habitat" data-endpoint="//trends.revcontent.com" data-widget-id="269417"></div> <script type="text/javascript" src="https://assets.revcontent.com/master/delivery.js" defer="defer"></script> </div>     <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Watch_this_video_SELLING_AT_CRAFT_FAIRS_My_Top_Tips22_mins_47_seconds"></span>Watch this video “SELLING AT CRAFT FAIRS | My Top Tips”(22 mins 47 seconds)<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <div class="rll-youtube-player" data-src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/XCjuUBYZ300" data-id="XCjuUBYZ300" data-query=""></div><noscript><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/XCjuUBYZ300" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></noscript>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Supplies"></span>Supplies:<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <ul><li>Table</li><li>Black tablecloths or sheets</li><li>Supplier logo</li><li>Catalogs, seasonal catalogs, mailing list check-in forms, monthly specials, product samples</li><li>Show directory</li><li>Door prize form, door prize box or bowl on clipboard</li><li>Price mark</li></ul>    <p>These are the items suitable for my papermaking business. Read these <a href="https://www.forbes.com/2008/04/08/online-craft-fair-tech-personal-cz_ccm_0408craft.html" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer">tips</a> and customize the display according to your product needs; perhaps vintage pieces or bright fabrics will be more suitable for your craft theme. I usually use 8-foot tables and smaller 6-foot tables. There are sales items on the 8-foot-high shelf, my signboard, and catalogs, door prizes and forms, mailing lists, specials, and some cards that I want to show to the booking party on the 6-foot-high table.</p><div class='code-block code-block-1' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-19"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=19" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=19" defer></script></div></div>     <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Table_Setup"></span>Table Setup:<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p>I prefer to use large black sheets because it covers the table better than any size tablecloth I have bought. I used a safety pin to pin my Stampin’ logo on the front of an 8-foot table. The change in height will increase the depth and size of the table, so please select the display items that can increase the shopping basket, photo box and layered store display.<br>Don’t set the table when you’re overcrowded, because it’s too extravagant and it’s easy to go astray. Customers will be afraid to touch and see anything because they may bump into other products or knock down things. unfriendly. Spread out things and put something until there is enough space to hold these things.</p><div class='code-block code-block-2' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-28"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=28" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=28" defer></script></div></div>     <p><br>I found another useful thing is the “less is more” theory. I put the inventory under the table in a plastic box under the bed box. If the customer is looking for a specific color, I can pull it out of the trash can to avoid crowding the table. As the inventory sells, I will sort things and add more products under the table.</p><div class='code-block code-block-3' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-2"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=2" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=2" defer></script></div></div>     <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Signage"></span>Signage:<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p>There is an easy-to-recognize large supplier logo so that everyone knows what products you sell. Note: Please stand up next to your table, <a href="https://www.ponfish.com/craft-show-booth-size-single-vs-double/" data-wpel-link="exclude">booth </a>or tent. It is important to stand up and arouse real interest from shoppers. There is nothing worse than a seller who hides behind a table and sits in a chair reading a book, and pays no attention to those lovely people who spend time shopping at the event. Customers will be afraid to talk to you so as not to disturb what you do. Don’t let it happen-stay alert, be friendly and stand up to meet them. When there are no shoppers, you can sit down.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Price"></span>Price:<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p>It is important to provide prices to customers. I don’t want my customers to search for prices and be shocked by the prices, so I want to show the prices clearly. I used color card paper with the product name and price printed on it. If you plan to perform frequently, it is a good idea to fit the logo.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Categories_display"></span>Categories display:<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <p>I found a three-layer wicker magazine basket at Pier 1 Imports, which was very suitable for my needs. I put a large catalog in the back, seasonal products in the front, and paper and fabric samples designed by famous designers in a small pocket in the front. In front is the yellow door prize vase. I think it adds something to the display. Other vendors who want to network and place orders can easily access business cards. I have a lot of pens to fill out the door prize form and write the party reservation date on the party postcard I use.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="This_is_a_review_and_some_other_tips_and_tricks"></span>This is a review and some other tips and tricks:<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <ul><li>With a piece of paper, it’s bigger.</li><li>Don’t be overcrowded; you don’t have to spend all your money!</li><li>Draw a picture of the door prize and explain what the prize is.</li><li>Use different heights.</li><li>Invest in catalogs/information display boards.</li><li>There are business cards available.</li><li>stand up! There is nothing worse than an uninterested seller.</li><li>Talk to customers and provide help them find what they want.</li><li>Ask them if they have heard of your product.</li><li>Ask them if they are interested in ordering anything or getting together with friends for free courses.</li></ul>    <p>These are my main tips for building a successful craft exhibition to attract customers and attract them to engage in your business. I really like craft shows-it gives shoppers the opportunity to buy local goods, get handmade gifts, book parties, it will make them creative sales channels and have fun with friends, and let me connect with other suppliers . This is a way to serve the community and make new friends.</p> <div class="related-posts"><h6>Related Posts</h6><ol><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-make-a-prize-wheel-cardboard-diy-prize-wheel/" title="Question: How To Make A Prize Wheel Cardboard Diy Prize Wheel" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: How To Make A Prize Wheel Cardboard Diy Prize Wheel</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-diy-a-prize-wheel/" title="Question: How To Diy A Prize Wheel" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: How To Diy A Prize Wheel</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-make-diy-prize-ribbon/" title="How To Make Diy Prize Ribbon" data-wpel-link="internal">How To Make Diy Prize Ribbon</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/what-is-a-craft-fair/" title="What Is A Craft Fair" data-wpel-link="internal">What Is A Craft Fair</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/do-tips-take-plasterboard/" title="Do Tips Take Plasterboard" data-wpel-link="internal">Do Tips Take Plasterboard</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/can-you-craft-dart-tips-on-a-skiller/" title="Question: Can You Craft Dart Tips On A Skiller" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: Can You Craft Dart Tips On A Skiller</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-make-a-diy-prize-wheel/" title="How To Make A Diy Prize Wheel" data-wpel-link="internal">How To Make A Diy Prize Wheel</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-make-a-prize-wheel-diy/" title="How To Make A Prize Wheel Diy" data-wpel-link="internal">How To Make A Prize Wheel Diy</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-plan-craft-fair-inventory/" title="Question: How To Plan Craft Fair Inventory" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: How To Plan Craft Fair Inventory</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-advertise-a-craft-fair/" title="Question: How To Advertise A Craft Fair" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: How To Advertise A Craft Fair</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-organize-a-craft-fair/" title="Quick Answer: How To Organize A Craft Fair" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: How To Organize A Craft Fair</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-run-a-craft-fair/" title="How To Run A Craft Fair" data-wpel-link="internal">How To Run A Craft Fair</a></li></ol></div><div class='code-block code-block-5' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div class="outbrain-tm" id="86299-16"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=16" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=16" defer></script></div></div> <!-- AI CONTENT END 2 --> 	]]></content:encoded>
<guid isPermaLink="false">6271e443e99f9</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 02:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.seniorcareto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/Craft-Fair-Tips.jpg" /></item>
<item>
<title><![CDATA[How to Safely Store Breast Milk? - Seniorcareto]]></title>
<link>https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/how-to-safely-store-breast-milk/</link>
<description><![CDATA[Table of Contents Watch this video “HOW TO PROPERLY STORE, FREEZE, &#038; THAW YOUR BREASTMILK”(10mins 31 seconds) After each pumping, you can: Keep the milk at room temperature. Use ice packs. Whether you choose refrigerated or frozen milk, you should: Breast milk storage solutions Bags bottled Guidelines for the safe storage of breast milk Room&hellip; &lt;a class=&quot;more-link&quot; href=&quot;http://afru.shop/hello-world/&quot;&gt;Continue reading &lt;span class=&quot;screen-reader-text&quot;&gt;Hello world!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;]]></description>
<content:encoded><![CDATA[  		<div id="ez-toc-container" class="ez-toc-v2_0_19 counter-hierarchy counter-decimal ez-toc-grey"> <div class="ez-toc-title-container"> <p class="ez-toc-title">Table of Contents</p> <span class="ez-toc-title-toggle"><a class="ez-toc-pull-right ez-toc-btn ez-toc-btn-xs ez-toc-btn-default ez-toc-toggle" style="display: none;"><i class="ez-toc-glyphicon ez-toc-icon-toggle"></i></a></span></div> <nav><ul class="ez-toc-list ez-toc-list-level-1"><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-1" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/how-to-safely-store-breast-milk/#Watch_this_video_HOW_TO_PROPERLY_STORE_FREEZE_THAW_YOUR_BREASTMILK10mins_31_seconds" title="Watch this video “HOW TO PROPERLY STORE, FREEZE, & THAW YOUR BREASTMILK”(10mins 31 seconds)">Watch this video “HOW TO PROPERLY STORE, FREEZE, & THAW YOUR BREASTMILK”(10mins 31 seconds)</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-2" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/how-to-safely-store-breast-milk/#After_each_pumping_you_can" title="After each pumping, you can:">After each pumping, you can:</a><ul class="ez-toc-list-level-3"><li class="ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-3" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/how-to-safely-store-breast-milk/#Keep_the_milk_at_room_temperature" title="Keep the milk at room temperature. ">Keep the milk at room temperature. </a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-4" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/how-to-safely-store-breast-milk/#Use_ice_packs" title=" Use ice packs. "> Use ice packs. </a></li></ul></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-5" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/how-to-safely-store-breast-milk/#Whether_you_choose_refrigerated_or_frozen_milk_you_should" title="Whether you choose refrigerated or frozen milk, you should:">Whether you choose refrigerated or frozen milk, you should:</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-6" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/how-to-safely-store-breast-milk/#Breast_milk_storage_solutions" title="Breast milk storage solutions">Breast milk storage solutions</a><ul class="ez-toc-list-level-3"><li class="ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-7" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/how-to-safely-store-breast-milk/#Bags" title=" Bags"> Bags</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-8" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/how-to-safely-store-breast-milk/#bottled" title="bottled">bottled</a></li></ul></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-2"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-9" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/how-to-safely-store-breast-milk/#Guidelines_for_the_safe_storage_of_breast_milk" title="Guidelines for the safe storage of breast milk">Guidelines for the safe storage of breast milk</a><ul class="ez-toc-list-level-3"><li class="ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-10" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/how-to-safely-store-breast-milk/#Room_temperature" title=" Room temperature"> Room temperature</a></li><li class="ez-toc-page-1 ez-toc-heading-level-3"><a class="ez-toc-link ez-toc-heading-11" href="https://www.seniorcareto.com/2020/06/how-to-safely-store-breast-milk/#In_refrigerator" title="In refrigerator">In refrigerator</a></li></ul></li></ul></nav></div>  <p>If you are breastfeeding your baby and want to work again, you may need to start expressing milk and storing it for future use. Expression and storage can also make your routine more flexible. For the <a href="https://www.ponfish.com/how-to-get-a-breast-pump-through-insurance/" data-wpel-link="exclude">safety </a>of infants, breast milk needs to be stored safely. Read tips on storing breast milk.</p><div class='code-block code-block-4' style='margin: 8px 0; clear: both;'> <div id="rc-widget-17a600" data-rc-widget data-widget-host="habitat" data-endpoint="//trends.revcontent.com" data-widget-id="269417"></div> <script type="text/javascript" src="https://assets.revcontent.com/master/delivery.js" defer="defer"></script> </div>     <p>The way you store breast milk depends on how long you want to use it. If you plan to use it within a few days, refrigeration is better than freezing. Frozen milk will mean that it loses some nutrition to fight infection, but frozen breast milk is still better for infants than formula milk.</p><div class='code-block code-block-1' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-19"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=19" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=19" defer></script></div></div>     <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Watch_this_video_HOW_TO_PROPERLY_STORE_FREEZE_THAW_YOUR_BREASTMILK10mins_31_seconds"></span>Watch this video “HOW TO PROPERLY STORE, FREEZE, & THAW YOUR BREASTMILK”(10mins 31 seconds)<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <div class="rll-youtube-player" data-src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/louYDE79wdk" data-id="louYDE79wdk" data-query=""></div><noscript><iframe loading="lazy" width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/louYDE79wdk" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></noscript>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="After_each_pumping_you_can"></span>After each pumping, you can:<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Keep_the_milk_at_room_temperature"></span>Keep the milk at room temperature. <span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <p>After pumping at room temperature (up to 77°F), breast milk can last 4 hours.<br>refrigeration. Breast milk can be kept in the refrigerator for 4 days.<br>Put the milk in the refrigerator. If you do not plan to use refrigerated breast milk within 4 days after pumping, please freeze it immediately after pumping.</p><div class='code-block code-block-2' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-28"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=28" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=28" defer></script></div></div>     <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Use_ice_packs"></span><br>Use ice packs. <span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <p>After pumping, you can put breast milk in a refrigerated or insulated refrigerated bag with a frozen ice pack for up to 24 hours. After 24 hours in the cooler, breast milk should be refrigerated or frozen.<br></p><div class='code-block code-block-3' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div id="86299-2"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=2" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=2" defer></script></div></div>     <p>When storing breast milk, use a <a href="https://www.cdc.gov/breastfeeding/recommendations/handling_breastmilk.htm" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer">breast milk storage</a> bag for freezing breast milk. You can also use clean glass bottles or rigid BPA-free plastic bottles with tight caps. Do not use containers with a recycling number of 7, which may contain BPA. Do not use disposable bottle linings or other plastic bags to store breast milk.</p>    <p>Storage bottles or storage bags for refrigerated or frozen breast milk can also be used as tax-deductible breastfeeding tools. In addition to breast pumps, most insurance plans must also cover breastfeeding supplies, such as storage bags. Call your insurance company for more information.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Whether_you_choose_refrigerated_or_frozen_milk_you_should"></span>Whether you choose refrigerated or frozen milk, you should:<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <ul><li>Use sterile containers. Choose plastic bottles or plastic breast milk bags. The glass bottle may crack or shatter.</li><li>Label and date bottles and bags, then use up the oldest bottles and bags first.</li><li>Keep the breast pump clean. Wash the parts in hot soapy water and rinse them thoroughly before disinfecting.</li><li>Wash your hands before milking and handling breast milk. Keep everything as clean as possible to reduce the possibility of bacteria growing in the stored milk.</li></ul>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Breast_milk_storage_solutions"></span>Breast milk storage solutions<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Bags"></span><br>Bags<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <p><br>If you are using a storage bag, fill it up to three quarters to allow expansion when frozen. To avoid chaos caused by the storage bag tearing, you may need to put the storage bag in a sealed plastic container.</p>    <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="bottled"></span>bottled<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <p><br>Many breast pumps come with some bottles, you can use them to store milk and give it to your baby, you can buy more if needed. You can also use regular baby bottles, even the cups with lids can be closed tightly. Fill three-quarters again to expand when the bottle freezes.</p>    <p>Whether you are using a bottle or a bag, you should try to avoid BPA. This BPA is a chemical found in certain plastics. This chemical has been shown to affect the endocrine system in animal studies. Babies are especially problematic. Avoid using bottles with the number 7 recycling symbol and the letters PC, because many of them contain BPA.</p>    <p>Although not very common, you can also find BPA-free milk storage bags. If your milk is to be stored in a <a href="https://www.seniorcare2share.com/2020/06/working-at-home-as-a-family-carer/" data-wpel-link="external" rel="nofollow external noopener noreferrer">day care</a> facility or other childcare facility, please make sure that the child’s name and date are clearly marked on the milk.</p>    <p>Remember, you don’t have to heat breast milk. If you haven’t done so already, it’s best to avoid letting your little children get into the habit of taking hot milk, because this is an extra step and has no health benefits. However, if you want to heat or thaw breast milk, make sure not to use a microwave. Doing so can interfere with nutrition and cause uneven heating of the milk, which can accidentally burn your baby’s mouth. It is best to warm the milk with warm water (rather than hot water) and then test it before feeding the baby. Make sure the top of the bottle is firm to prevent water from entering the container and contaminating the container.</p>    <h2><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Guidelines_for_the_safe_storage_of_breast_milk"></span>Guidelines for the safe storage of breast milk<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h2>    <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="Room_temperature"></span> Room temperature<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <p><br>Newly extracted breast milk can be stored at room temperature (not higher than 77 degrees Fahrenheit). Ideally, they can be stored for up to four hours as long as they are not in direct sunlight or near other heat sources. In some cases, it may be able to be stored at room temperature for up to six hours, especially if it is not so warm or the room is on the cooler side.</p>    <h3><span class="ez-toc-section" id="In_refrigerator"></span>In refrigerator<span class="ez-toc-section-end"></span></h3>    <p><br>Breast milk can be kept in the refrigerator for up to four days. Check the temperature of the refrigerator to make sure it is around 40 degrees Fahrenheit and store the loot on the back of the coldest refrigerator. Avoid placing breast milk on the refrigerator door, because when the door is opened, the refrigerator is most susceptible to warm air. Four days later, it’s time to move the milk to the refrigerator.</p>    <p>This is general information and cannot replace your healthcare provider’s advice. If you have a problem that cannot be solved quickly, please seek help immediately. Every baby is different. If in doubt, please contact your doctor or healthcare provider.</p> <div class="related-posts"><h6>Related Posts</h6><ol><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-breast-milk-good-for-seniors/" title="Is Breast Milk Good For Seniors" data-wpel-link="internal">Is Breast Milk Good For Seniors</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-make-breast-milk-jewelry-diy/" title="How To Make Breast Milk Jewelry Diy" data-wpel-link="internal">How To Make Breast Milk Jewelry Diy</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-it-ok-to-store-milk-in-stainless-steel/" title="Quick Answer: Is It Ok To Store Milk In Stainless Steel" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: Is It Ok To Store Milk In Stainless Steel</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/is-it-better-to-store-milk-in-glass-or-plastic/" title="Is It Better To Store Milk In Glass Or Plastic" data-wpel-link="internal">Is It Better To Store Milk In Glass Or Plastic</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-o-craft-safely/" title="Question: How O Craft Safely" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: How O Craft Safely</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-unfreeze-chicken-breast/" title="Quick Answer: How To Unfreeze Chicken Breast" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: How To Unfreeze Chicken Breast</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-unthaw-chicken-breast-fast/" title="How To Unthaw Chicken Breast Fast" data-wpel-link="internal">How To Unthaw Chicken Breast Fast</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-diy-breast-lift-tape/" title="Quick Answer: How To Diy Breast Lift Tape" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: How To Diy Breast Lift Tape</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-make-diy-breast-pump/" title="Question: How To Make Diy Breast Pump" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: How To Make Diy Breast Pump</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-do-you-melt-plastic-safely/" title="Question: How Do You Melt Plastic Safely" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: How Do You Melt Plastic Safely</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-do-you-transport-cakes-safely/" title="Question: How Do You Transport Cakes Safely" data-wpel-link="internal">Question: How Do You Transport Cakes Safely</a></li><li><a href="http://www.seniorcareto.com/how-to-safely-remove-ceramic-tile/" title="Quick Answer: How To Safely Remove Ceramic Tile" data-wpel-link="internal">Quick Answer: How To Safely Remove Ceramic Tile</a></li></ol></div><div class='code-block code-block-5' style='margin: 8px auto; text-align: center; display: block; clear: both;'> <div class="outbrain-tm" id="86299-16"><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/gen.js?type=16" defer></script><script src="http://ads.themoneytizer.com/s/requestform.js?siteId=86299&formatId=16" defer></script></div></div> <!-- AI CONTENT END 2 --> 	]]></content:encoded>
<guid isPermaLink="false">6271e443e9f18</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 02:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
<media:content medium="image" url="https://www.seniorcareto.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/How-to-Safely-Store-Breast-Milk.jpg" /></item>
</channel>
</rss>
